Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Maps, Series I
  - Topographic Maps. United States., 000003
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grano scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10130/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000184
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Maddock scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: 47099-H5-TF-024 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000198
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mc Kenzie scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10015/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000201
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: West Hope scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000220
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: West Hope SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000221
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Velva scale: 1:65200 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10045/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000231
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Devils Lake scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W9845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000290
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Devils Lake Mountain scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W9830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000291
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kuroki scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000342
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Driscoll scale: 1:62 500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10000/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000563
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Williston scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10400/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000623
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Willow City scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000216
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Tunbridge scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000238
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Landa SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000365
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Roth scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000507
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Round Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000508
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Souris scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000532
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Souris SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000533
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Souris SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000534
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Upham NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1955; 000234
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rangeley NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1955; 000305
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rangeley NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1955; 000306
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fonda scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1955; 000425
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dunseith scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1955; 000562
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Enmet scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000246
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Enmet NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000247
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Douglas West scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000294
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Makoti SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000375
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Carbury scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000399
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Minot scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000409
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blackwater Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000474
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blackwater Lake SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000475
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blue Hill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000478
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Berlin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W9822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000496
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Roseglen scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000510
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rangeley scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000304
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rangeley SE scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000307
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Karlsruhe scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000353
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bergen scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000495
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Marlow scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4552.5-W9722.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000200
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Drake scale: 1: 62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000295
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Drake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000296
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Drake NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000297
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Drake SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000298
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Drake SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000299
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kongsberg scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-w10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000345
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kief scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000349
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Clifton scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N7100-H2-TF-024 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000393
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Balfour scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10030/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000480
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Balfour scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000481
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Balfour NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000482
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000486
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sperati Point scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10322.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000584
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sperati Point scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10322.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000585
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lone Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10307.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000586
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Long X Divide scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10315/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000587
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: McClusky scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10200/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000615
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Watford City scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10400/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000616
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bismarck scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10200/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000617
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Williston scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10400/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000618
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dickinson scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10400/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000622
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000402
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10030-7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000403
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000404
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000405
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000406
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Pickardville scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000437
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: South West Fargo scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W9652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000530
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Leihigh scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10237.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000578
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dickinson scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000591
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dickinson South scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000592
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Glen Ullin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000268
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dengate scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000286
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Denhoff scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000287
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Heart Butte scale: 1:24000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000334
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Heart Butte NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000335
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Horse Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000336
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lincoln Valley scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000355
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lincoln Valley scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000371
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Florence Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000426
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: North Almont scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: n4645-w10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000427
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: New Salem scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000450
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Barrie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W9700/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000488
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: White Butte E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10215/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000605
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: White Butte NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10222.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000606
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: White Butte NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10215/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000607
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: White Butte W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10222.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000608
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Washburn scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000225
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Washburn NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000227
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Underwood scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000237
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Creek NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10045/75 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000240
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Creek NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000241
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Creek SE scale: 1:24 000` Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000242
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Creek SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000243
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000245
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lake Nettie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-w10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000370
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Menoken scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10030/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000408
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Peterson Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000436
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rocky Ridge scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10315/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000580
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Daglum scale: 1:62 500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10300/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000590
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mandan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000199
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Harmon scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000326
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Menoken SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000401
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Burnt Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000485
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bismarck scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000501
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Schmidt scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: n4637.5-w10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000521
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sugarloaf Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000552
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fryburg NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5W101315/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000574
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Belfield scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10307.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000596
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Belfield NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5W10300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000597
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Belfield SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000598
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Belfield SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10307.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000599
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Davis Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10237.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000601
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Park River scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W9737.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000435
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fairfield SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000571
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fairfield scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10307.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000572
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hungry Man Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707-W101300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000575
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rattlesnake Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10307.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000581
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Leverich scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000356
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Index to Top Maps of ND scale: 1:1 000 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N46-W104 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000625
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Johnsons Corner scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4744-W10252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000576
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Keene scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000577
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blue Buttes scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000589
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blue Buttes scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000593
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Charlson scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000594
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Charlson NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000595
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Charlson NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000600
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wilton scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000214
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wilton SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000215
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Price scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000416
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sanger scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000502
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Index to Top Maps of ND scale: 1: 1 000 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N46-W104 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000626
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Washburn SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000228
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Enmet SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000248
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Enmet SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000249
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blackwater Lake SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000476
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blackwater Lake SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000477
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Stanton SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000528
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sanish SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10237.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000583
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bismarck scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10200/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000621
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Medicine Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000204
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Medicine Butte NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000205
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Clark scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000254
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Clark NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000255